



# **Anass Assim**

**Date of birth:** 24/01/2002 **Phone number:** (+34) 662055990

Email address: anass.assim.2010@gmail.com 
Github: github.com/ciscoAnass

in LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/anass-assim/?locale=en\_US

**Website:** www.anass-assim.com/index-en.html

#### **ABOUT ME**

Systems and network administrator with experience in managing technological infrastructures. I stand out for my communication skills, teamwork and proactive attitude. Fluent in English, Spanish, French and Arabic, I work well under pressure and am committed to continuous learning to deliver efficient solutions.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Equipment Assembly Tech**

**casaconfig.ma** [ 06/2024 – 09/2024 ]

City: Casablanca | Country: Morocco

System Assembly: Assembly and cooling.

• Compatibility: BIOS/UEFI selection and configuration.

• OS installation: Windows and Linux.

· Maintenance: Diagnostics and testing.

# **Junior Sys Admin**

**DIGITAL HARD** [ 09/2021 - 09/2022 ]

City: Casablanca | Country: Morocco

• Servers: Configure and maintain Windows/Linux.

• VMs: Manage with VMware.

• Automation: Scripts with PowerShell/Bash and Ansible.

Monitoring: Grafana and Nagios.

• Documentation: Keep up to date.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## **Network Computer Systems Administration**

*I.E.S Rodrigo Caro* [ 09/2023 – Current ]

City: Seville | Country: Spain | Website: fprodrigocaro.org

## Computer network specialist technician

**CFMOTI NTIC 1** [ 09/2019 – 06/2021 ]

City: Casablanca | Country: Morocco

# **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Linux Administration / Virtualization / SQL Databases / Windows Client and Server / Web Development: HTML, CSS, JS / Network Protocols / Automation / Monitoring / Microsoft Office / Computer Maintenance

# **LANGUAGES**

**English: Very High** 

Spanish: Very HighFrench: High

· Arabic: Native